Guide to the Ladyslipper, Inc. Records, 1965-2011 and undated RL.10140
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Ladyslipper, Inc. records
1965-2011 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Ladyslipper, Inc.
RL.10140
190.5 Linear Feet 127 boxes
Ladyslipper Music is a North Carolina non-profit organization which has been involved in many facets of women's music since 1976. Their mission is to heighten public awareness of the achievements of women artists and musicians, and to expand the scope and availability of musical and literary recordings by women. This collection documents the history, activities, and output of this organization.
Provenance
The Ladyslipper Music Inc. Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in February 2002, December 2010, and October 2012. Acquired by the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Arrangement
Generally alphabetical. Original order and folder titles maintained.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Biographical / Historical
Ladyslipper, Inc. began 1976 in Durham, N.C. as a 4-page resource guide devoted to the musical accomplishments of women artists. Their initial mission was to fill the need for information about women in music, as well as to increase the accessibility of women's recordings. Their original guide eventually grew into the Catalog and Resource Guide of Music by Women, which became their signature publication. Ladyslipper grew alongside the second wave of the women's movement, inspired by women's music, arts, culture, and ideas. The organization became a nexus of women's activism and culture, both locally in Durham, and regionally in the Southeast, sponsoring many women's music events and gatherings. Ladyslipper is also a small, independent music label dedicated to issuing and promoting the work of innovative women artists.
More information about the organization and its activities can be found on its website: https://www.ladyslipper.org/
Collection Overview
Collection documents this nonprofit organization dedicated to identifying, issuing, and promoting women's music. It consists of their financial records, including customer files, vendor files, retail and wholesale sales documentation; a complete run of their Catalog and Resource Guide of Music by Women, production materials used to create the guide including art and graphics, and other marketing and promotional materials, including advertisements. It also includes documentation of sponsored concerts and festivals, clippings, and extensive documentation of all administrative activities of the organization. It also includes copies audio materials produced and distributed by Ladyslipper, including master copies of recordings.
Conditions Governing Access
Original audiovisual materials closed to patron use.
Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture; Ladyslipper, Inc.
- Accession (1995-0089) (3000 items; 6 lin. ft.; dated 1976-1995)
  Scope and Contents
  Contains the publisher's negatives for the company's wholesale and retail catalogs, which feature women musicians and composers.
  - Publisher's negatives for the company's wholesale and retail catalogs featuring women musicians and composers. (Box 1-4)
- Accession (2002-0247) (40 items; .6 lin. ft.; dated 1978-2002)
  - Copies of the Ladyslipper Catalog and Resource Guide; issues for 1978, 1980-1983, and 1987-2002. (Box 1)
- Financial Series, 1975-2007; 1
  - Customer Files subseries, 1975-2007; 1.1
    - Adam Male, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 1)
    - A Different Drummer Books (2 folders), 1991-2002 (Box 1)
    - A Different Light, 1997; 1 folders (Box 1)
    - Affinity Books, 1995-2001; 1 folders (Box 1)
    - Afternoons and Coffee Spoons Shop, 1996-2000; 1 folders (Box 1)
    - After Stonewall, 1991-2001; 1 folders (Box 1)
    - Afterwords, 1993-2001; 1 folders (Box 1)
    - Albany Civil Rights, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 1)
    - Alliance Entertainment Co (5 folders), 1997-2003 (Box 1)
    - Alternative Creations, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 1)
    - Alternatives, 1997-2002; 1 folders (Box 1)
    - Amazon.com, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 1)
    - Amazon Bookstore (3 folders), 1985-2002 (Box 1)
    - Amoeba Music, Berkeley (2 folders), 1997-2002 (Box 2)
    - Amoeba Music, Los Angeles, 2002; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Amy Kristine's, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Andover Gift Shop, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Annapurna Herb Shop, 1997; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - An Open Book, 1994-2000; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Antigone Books (3 folders), 1979-2002 (Box 2)
    - Apara Borrows, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Apple Valley Books, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Aradia Bookstore, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Artesian Wellness, 2000; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Artistic Amazon, 1997-2002; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Artisan Gift Shop, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Ashram Books and Crafts, 1989-2001; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Asungi Productions, 1999; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Athena Gifts, 1994-2002; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Atlantis, 2000; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - At Sara's Table, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Atoda.com, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Aura Soma Lava, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Awareness, 2000; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - The Back Door, 1999; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Backpages, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Backroads, 1993-2004; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Two of a Kind, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - The Bag Lady, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Bailey Coy, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Bajo El Sol, 1999; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Banyen Sound, 1991-2002; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Barjon's Books, 1986-2002; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Barking Dog Music, 1993-2000; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Bashiri Spiritual Bazaar, 1998; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Susan Banes-COPE, 2000; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Bayside Distribution, 1992-2002; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Beauty with Balance, 1992-1998; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Belly Dance Saray, 1997; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Beedazzled, 1999; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Beneath A Wizard's Moon, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Betty Webb's Ltd, 1999; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Birchmere, 1989-2001; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Bloodroot, 1977-2002; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Bluestrockings, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Boadecia's Books, Inc., 1992-2001; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Body Expression, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Bonner's Books, 1992-2002; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - Book House of Stuyvesant, 1993-2000; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - The Book Cellar, 1988-2001; 1 folders (Box 2)
    - The Book Gallery, 1 folders (Box 2)
    - The Book Garden, 1992-2003; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Bookspan, 1995-2006; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Book-Woman (3 folders), 1978-2002 (Box 3)
    - Boston Gay Men's Chorus, 1997-2000; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - BricBrac'N Brass, 1999; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Brigit Books (3 folders), 1989-2002 (Box 3)
    - Brushstrokes (2 folders), 1994-2001 (Box 3)
    - By the Light of the Moon, 1995-2000; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Caesar Rodney School District, 1998; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Caf? Monet, 1993-1998; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - The Dreaming Goddess/Call of the Wild, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Calamus Bookstore, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Calistoga Bookstore, 1994-2001; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - California Video Institute, 1993-1996; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Camp Pleiades, 1999; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Canadian River Music, 1995-1998; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Carmichael's Bookstore, 1994-1998; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - National Marketing, 1997-1999; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Cat and the Fiddle, 1996-1998; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Category 6 Books, 1986-2002; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - CD Warehouse, 1999; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Celebration - Colorado, 1986-2002; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - The Celtic Cottage, 1998; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Center of Pastoral Care, 1999; 1 folders (Box 3)
    - Charis Books and More (2 folders), 1993-2002 (Box 3)
    - Charis Books and More (3 folders), 1978-1993 (Box 4)
    - The Children's Bookstore, 1993-1998; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Chinaberry Book Service, 1987-1999; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Chinatown Enterprises, 1995-1998; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Choices Unlimited, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Choyces Arts and Crafts, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Goddess Connection Cindy Miller, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Circle of Aradia, 1998; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Circle Sanctuary, 1990-2002; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Circle of Stones, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Charmacy Wildlife Center, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Classical Film and Music, 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Clearings, 1992-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Cliff Dwellers Lodge, 1998; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - The Closet, 1997; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Country Crafters and Antiques, 2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - The United Methodist Publishing House, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Asheville-Buncombe Tech, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Avila College, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Cornell College (2 folders), 1997-1998 (Box 4)
    - Greer Music Library, 2000; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Dickinson College Library, 1999; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Color of Women, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Old Dominion University, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Common Language, 1989-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Copperfield's Music, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Copperfield's Books, 1987-2000; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Cornucopia, 1996; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Coyote Moon, 1992-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Crafters and Cnadles, 1997; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - The Crane Bag, 1997-1999; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Crazy Ladies Bookstore, 1979-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Crazy Wisdom, 1986-2000; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Cresent Moon Goddess, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Creative Native Productions, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Crizmac, 1998; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Crone's Cave, 1997; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Crone's Cupboard, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Crystal Enchantment, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - The Crystal Fox, 1991-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Crystal Visions, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Zephyr Books Music and Gifts/Crystal Wonders, 1988-1998; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Curt's Shirts and Gifts, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Cutting Edge Press, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Dark Star Books and Music, 1995-1997; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Curve Magazine, 1994-1999; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Diana's Grove, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Diverse Universe, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Does Your Father Know, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Dorothy Abbott, 1997; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Dorothy's Surrender, 1994-2002; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Downtown Books, 1994-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Down to Earth, 2000; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Dragon's Breath, Ltd., 1997; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Moon Dance/Dreamweaver, 1991-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Eagle Rose, 1999; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Eagletons, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Casting Journeys/Earthsongs, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Earth Spirit, Inc., 1998; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Earth Friendly Books, 1998; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Earth Rhythms, 1995-2001; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Earth Wisdom Music, 1981-2002; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Earth Tones Studios, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Earth Tree, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - East West Bookshop, 1994-2002; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Echodisc, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - E.D.'s Gourmet Records, 1998-2000; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Elements, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Enchantments, Inc., 1991-2000; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Epic Bookshop, 1998; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Equinox Books, 1995-1998; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Esoterica, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Essentials, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Evaleon Hill, 1996; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Evergreen State College Bookstore, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - S. Evyn Rubin, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Phillips Exeter Academy, 2003; 1 folders (Box 4)
    - Faith and Recovery, 2000; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Family Music Connection, 1999; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Fantastic Records, 1996-1998; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Fatima's Bazaar and Cultural Dance Studio, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Faubourg Morigny Books (2 folders), 1987-1998 (Box 5)
    - Femail Creations, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - The Feminist Bookshop, 1979-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - The Center for Feminine Studies, 2000; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Fibers & Fantasy, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Fitchburg State College, 1997; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Flight of the Phoenix, 1993-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Judy Flavell, 1997; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Fly By Night, 1996-2001; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Follett Media Distribution, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Food For Humans, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Footlight Records, 1997-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Footnotes, 1997; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Foundry Music, 1995-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Frauenbuchladen-Hamburg, 1995-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Frauenbuchladen-Zurich, 1984-1998; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Full Circle Books, 1979-1998; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Gabriel's Downtown, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Gaia Bookstore, 1989-2000; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Clara Van Gastel, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Gateway Garden, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Gaymart Enterprises, Inc., 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Gay Wired, 1996-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - The Gazebo, 1998; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Get Booked, 1993-2001; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - The Gift Horse and Bookshelf, 1995-2000; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Girlfriends Coffee House and Book Store, 1995-1998; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Giovanni's Room (3 folders), 1985-2002 (Box 5)
    - Girls and Company, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Glad Day Bookstore, 1987-2000; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Global Village, 1989-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Goddess Connection, 1998; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - The Goddess Store, 1997-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Goldenrod Consignment Account, 2003; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Golden Gull, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - The GTU Bookstore, 1991-2002; 1 folders (Box 5)
    - Grailville Art and Bookshop, 1995-2000; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Grand Books, 1991; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Grapevine Books (Reno, NV), 1992-2001; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Grassroots Books, 1992-1993; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Grass Roots Bookstore, 1985-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Grateful Heart, 1989-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Green Moon, 1998; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Greenfield Herb Garden, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Green Gables Bookstore, 1993-1997; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Greenwood Pier Country Store, 1993-1998; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - The Grizz's Den, 1996; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Grapevine Books (Boone, NC), 1994-2001; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Gualala Books, 1994-2000; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Gulf of Maine Books, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Gulliver's Living and Learning Center, 1997; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Gypsy Moon, 1992-1999; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Gypsy, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Hand of Aries, II, 1991-2000; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Harmonious Balance, 1996-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Hardwood Software Inc, 1996-1998; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Harmony Ridge Music, 1996-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Hawk Wind Trading Post, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Healing Arts Center, 1990-2001; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Healing Earth Resources, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Heal the Planet, 1999; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Healthy Sounds, 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Hear Again CD's Inc, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Healing Rays, 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Heart 'N Home (Cape Coral, FL), 1994-1996; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Going to the Source/Heartlight, 1997-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Heart 'N Home (Bonita Springs, FL), 1999-2000; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Earthwise/Heart of the Goddess, 1992-2000; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Optimum Health Institute, 1998; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Hearts and Minds, 1986-1989; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Heart Stone, 1998; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Heavenly Noyse, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - 1998-2000, 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Leni Hedwig Kastl, 1996-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Henry's, 1996-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Herb Shop Records, 2000; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Here's to your Health, 1998; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Heritage Temple, 1999; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Herland: The Wanderground (Santa Cruz, CA), 1993-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Herland Sister Resources (Oklahoma City, OK), 1989-1994; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Her Place, 1993-1999; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Her Story, 1992-1999; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - The Hobbit Doorway Books and Gifts, 1994-1997; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Fatima Johnson/Rakkasah Convention, 2001; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Holland Compact Disc, 1990-1997; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Hollow Hills, 1997; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Hollyhock, 1997-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Horned Toad, 1999; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Hot Stuff, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - House of Musical Traditions, 1984-1998; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - House of Records, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Hearts of Light, 1994; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - I And I, 1997; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Idaho Women's Music Festival, 1997; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Image Design, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Indigenous Hands, 1998; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - In Heaven Lights, 2000; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - In Her Image, 1987-2000; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Inklings, 1988-1998; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - In Other Words, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Inspriations, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Intercall Systems, 1997; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Integrated Healthcare Systems, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Interface, 1994-1998; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Into the Light, 1997-2000; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - International Association of Reiki, 1997; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Interweave, 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - In Your Ear Music Emporium, 1994-1999; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Iona Press Bookstore, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Wild Iris Books, 1992-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Irresistible Rhythms MAILING LIST, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Irresistible Rhythms, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Isis Metaphysical Bookstore, 1991-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Island Rag Picker, 1997-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - Mainely A Cappella/Island Music, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - It's My Pleasure, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 6)
    - It's My Pleasure, 1991-1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Jane H. Johnson, 1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Jefferson City Correctional Center, 2000; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Jerry Egan Massage Therapy, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Jim Hawkin, 1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - The Jones Library, 1995-2003; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Jubilee: Global Gifts Ltd, 1996-2000; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Getting in Touch/Julie Corey, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Juniper and Sage, 1997; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Just Alan, 2000-2002; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - JV Fletcher Library (2 folders), 1995-2001 (Box 7)
    - Karins Sanctum of Transformation, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Kay Gardner--Sea Gnomes Musidc, 1995-2001; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Kazu FM, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Keepers of the Moon Garden, 1995-2000; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Keeper of the Moon, 1996-1997; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Kelley Music, 1997; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Kelley-Fletcher, 1995; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Kimberly's, 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Kindred Spirit Bookshop (Visalia, CA), 1990-1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Kindred Spirits Books (London, Ontario), 1993-2002; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Kripalu Shop, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Kulu Music, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - KZUM, 1991-1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Ladyslipper Consignment, 1993-2005; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Laho Chi Healing Center, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Lambda Rising (2 folders), 1992-2002 (Box 7)
    - Northern Lights/The Landing Disc & Tape, 1986-2002; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Lauristine Swain, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Library Acquisitions Service, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Albertsons Library, 1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Aurora Public Library, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Berkeley Public Library, 1995-2005; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - City of Boulder: Public Library, 1997; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Brooklyn Public Library, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Public Library of Cincinnati (2 folders), 1996-1999 (Box 7)
    - Columbus Metropolitan Library, 1997-1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - City of Covina: Library, 1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Crandall Public Library, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Cuyahoga County Public Library, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Elmhurst Public Library, 1997; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Evansville-Vanderburgh Library, 1997-1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Forest Grove City Library, 1998-2000; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Haywood County Public Library, 1996-1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Hoover Library Tech Services: Western Maryland College, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Indianapolis Marion County Public Library, 1995-1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Kenyon College: Olin/Chalmers Library, 1996-1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Loyola-Notre Dame Library, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - McCain Library, Agnes Scott College, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - McWherter Library, University of Memphis, 1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Milwaukee Public Library, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Newton Public Library, 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Thousand Oaks Library, 2001; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Conservatory Library, Oberlin College, 1998-2001; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Lake Oswego Public Library, 2000; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Patchogue-Medford Library, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Pearl River Public Library, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Plainsboro Free Public Library, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Port Townsend Public Library, 2000; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Portsmouth Public Library, 1995-1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Portland Public Library, 1997; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Rockford Public Library, 1997-1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Santa Barbara Public Library, 2000; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Sno-Isle Regional Library, 2000; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - South Kingstown Public Library, 1998; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - St. Louis County Library, 1995-1999; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Thomas Branigan Memorial Library, 2000; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Worcester County Library, 2001; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Little Luxuries, 1996-2000; 1 folders (Box 7)
    - Little Sisters, 1993-2001; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Living Bookends, 1990-2001; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Lobo Bookshop (2 folders), 1994-2002 (Box 8)
    - Lucia's Garden, 1986-2002; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Luminessence, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Macalester College, Dewitt Wallace Library, 1987-2000; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Magickal Arts, 1997-2001; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Magical Journey, 1993-2000; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Malaprop's Bookstore and Caf? (2 folders), 1993-2002 (Box 8)
    - Mama Bear's, 1992-2002; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Mamma Llama, 2000-2004; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Manifest Discs and Tapes, 1995-2002; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Manna Reading Center, 2000-2001; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Denver Women's Chorus, 2004; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Mast Academy, 2000; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Medusa's Magical Mysteries, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Melody (3 folders), 1984-2002 (Box 8)
    - Metamorphics Media, LLC, 1999-2001; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Women's Music and Memorabilia, 1998-2002; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Milk and Honey, 1996-2002; 1 folders (Box 8)
    - Millennium Music, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 8)